吸血鬼
Vampires.
每次听这字眼都觉得更好笑了
Gets funnier every time I hear it.
(忆往昔)
吸血鬼巢穴平均八到十人
Vampires nest in groups of 8 to 10.
受害人被带回巢穴  留一条命
Victims are taken to the nest where the pack keeps them alive,
被吸血数日甚至数周
bleeding them for days or weeks.
我们不砍吸血鬼的头
We don't decapitate vampires.
我们辐射他们
We irradiate them.
厉害
Cool.
玩具最好玩了
The toys are the fun part.
因为一些明显的原因  我们不信任那些英国人
For obvious reasons, we don't trust the Brits.
搞什么鬼  我们不是一队的吗
What the hell? Aren't we supposed to be on the same team?
我很了解这把柯尔特枪
I know all about the Colt.
所有生灵里只有五个
You know there's only five things in all Creation
它杀不掉
it can't kill?
你觉得妈妈会希望我们过这种生活吗
You think Mom would've wanted this for us?
对我而言  没什么比我的家庭更重要
Nothing comes before my family, not with me.
是吗
Really?
还是说那是你想去相信的
Or is that just what you want to believe?
你真是会撒谎  玛丽
You're an excellent liar, Mary.
可惜妈妈不能来
Too bad Mom couldn't make it.
是啊  我觉得她好像有什么事
Yeah. I feel like something's going on with her,
不肯说
and she ain't talkin' about it.
我一直在跟英国记录者合作
I have sort of been working with the British Men of Letters.
那我们怎么办
So where does that leave us?
(如今)
听我说完
Just hear me out.
求你们
Please.
无话可说
Just wow.
迪恩
Dean...
英国记录者所做的事
What the British Men of Letters are doing...
我们做的事  这样更好
what we're doing, it's a better way.
他们
They...
听着  我并不是认不清他们的面目
Look, I'm not blind to who they are
或是忘记了他们所做的
or what they've done,
-但是  -什么时候
- but - When?
什么时候  你什么时候开始跟他们合作的
When? When did you start working with them?
自从
Since...
湖边小屋那次之前
before the lake house.
不是沃利
It wasn't Wally.
那案子是他们给我的
They brought me that case.
你是替英国人跑腿
You were runnin' an errand for the Brits.
还瞒着我们
You kept it from us.
小卡差点没命
Cass almost died.
-我...  -一个猎人牺牲了
- I - A Hunter got killed.
你以为我不知道吗
Think I don't know?
是我火葬了他的尸体
I'm the one who burned his body.
是我去通知他妻子
I'm the one who told his wife.
我每晚都会看到他死去的那一幕
I watch him die every night.
很好
Good.
[邪恶力量 第12季第14集]
(三天后)
(准入)
今天干得不错
Nice work today.
我得说
I must say,
这个小玩意真是名不虚传
this little beauty certainly worked as advertised.
我们几乎不用费力气
We barely had to lift a finger.
AVD啊
Ah, the AVD.
我就喜欢新玩具
I do love a new toy.
玛丽
Mary?
一切都好吧
Everything all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
-凯奇  -塞琳娜
- Ketch. - Serena.
你正好要去军械库  麻烦了
Oh, you're headed past the Armory. If you wouldn't mind.
把东西拿出来  放回去
Unpack, reshelve,
我的枪需要擦了
and my Sig Sauer could use a good scrubbing.
我有三个博士学位
I have three PhDs.
我们都十分为你骄傲  亲爱的
And we're all very proud of you, luv.
(至迪恩  很抱歉让你这样知道  我可以解释  我们能不能谈谈  对不起  迪恩)
我是为了你们
I'm doing this for you.
我要赶上三十年的进度
I'm playing three decades of catch up here.
我们就不是吗
And we're not?
你以为我们是什么感受
How do you think this has been for us?
我们是你的儿子  而你一直不在
We're your sons, and you've been gone.
我们这辈子  你都不在
Our whole lives, you've been gone.
你说你需要时间  不  你说你需要空间
You said that you needed time. No, you said you need space.
我们就给了你空间
So we gave you your space.
但你不仅仅是需要空间
But you didn't need just space.
你是需要跟我们拉开距离
No, you needed space from us.
不是这样的
That's not true.
迪恩  我在努力...
Dean, I'm trying --
哪怕一次  你能不能努力做个妈妈
How 'bout for once, you just try to be a mom?
我是你母亲
I am your mother,
但我不仅仅是个"妈妈"
but I am not "just a mom."
你也不是孩子了
And you are not a child.
我从来都不是
I never was.
我们  或是他们
So between us and them --
不是那样的
It's not like that.
玛丽  就是的
Yeah, Mary, it is.
你做出了选择
And you made your choice.
门在那边
So there's the door.
(跟我说话吧)
萨姆
Sam...
你还是走吧
You should go.
又消灭了一个巢穴  简单轻松
Another nest terminated. No complications.
都有点  无聊了
Bit...boring, really.
很好  无聊是好事
Good. Well, boring's good.
玛丽怎么样了
And how's Mary?
很好  一如既往
Excellent. As always.
她提起她儿子了吗
She say anything about her boys?
我说过很多很多次了
As I've said many, many, so many times,
我们不需要他们
we don't need them.
我们已经有最厉害的温家人了
We already have the best Winchester.
是啊  但那不由你来决定
Yes. But that's not your call, is it?
也不由我
Or mine.
长老们要他们加入
The old men want them on board.
在伦敦看来
As far as London's concerned,
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特去哪
where Sam and Dean Winchester go,
其他美国猎人都会跟上
the rest of the American Hunters will follow.
亚克朗市有人死了
Dead guy in Akron.
尸体两天前被发现
Body found two days ago.
喉咙被完全划开  撕烂
Throat ripped out, ear-to-ear.
你也早啊
Well, good morning to you, too.
自己看看
Read it.
(男子遭割喉致死)
这人是个毒贩  有敌人
The guy was a-a known drug dealer with enemies.
他的喉咙没被撕烂  是用刀划开的
His throat wasn't ripped out. It was slit with a knife.
我觉得这可能不是我们的问题
I'm not really sure this is our kind of thing.
那未必  他的血或许被吸干了
We don't know that. His blood could've been drained.
或许被
It could've been?
这样吧  你给我们找件案子
You know what? You find us a case.
因为我需要马上打点什么
'Cause I need to hit something. Now.
-你想谈谈吗  -不想
- You wanna talk about it? - Not really.
她怎么想的啊
What was she thinkin', man?
我不知道
I don't know.
或许我们该问问她
Maybe we should ask her.
-什么  -听着
- What? - Look...
我也生气
I-I am pissed
也气恼  也不解
and -- and frustrated and confused, too.
但是  我们好几天不理她了
But we've frozen her out for days.
-她骗了我们  萨姆  -我知道
- She lied to us, Sam. - I know.
-骗了我们几个月  -我知道  但那是妈妈
- For months. - I know, but it's Mom!
不管她做了什么  她肯定有个好理由的
I mean, whatever she was doing, she must've had a good reason.
好理由  跟那些混球合作有好理由
A good reason? A good reason for working with those ass clowns?
听着  我明白你的意思
Look, I hear you, all right?
但是  说到底  她是家人
But -- but at the end of the day, she's family.
我们至少也该
We owe it to her to at least --
告诉你  不管了  我得喝一杯
All right, you know what? Screw it. I need a drink.
你...
You...
我需要多喝几杯
No, I need drinks. Plural.
还有
And this...
你这套和事佬的做派
whole peacemaker shtick that you've been running,
先是跟小卡  然后又是跟妈妈
first with Cass, now with Mom,
-太老套了  -那是什么意思
- it's getting old, man. - What's that supposed to mean?
你总是中立  萨姆
You're always playing the middle, Sam.
这一次  你能不能选个立场
For once, why don't you pick a side?
(玛丽  六条未读信息)
(玛丽  萨姆  给我个机会解释吧  萨姆  可以谈谈吗  对不起  接电话吧  萨姆  我们需要见面  急事)
(萨姆  我们需要见面  急事)
谢谢你来
Thanks for coming.
什么急事
What's so urgent?
萨姆  我搞砸了
Sam...I messed up.
我知道我搞砸了
I know I messed up.
但英国记录者做的事
But what the British Men of Letters are doing,
这比我们要紧  萨姆
this is bigger than us, Sam.
我们真的有机会
We've got a real shot here.
什么机会
Shot at what?
清除这世上的怪物
A world without monsters.
让你和迪恩再不用猎魔
A world where you and Dean don't have to hunt,
让你们过上正常生活
where you can have normal lives.
我选择了这份生活
I chose this life.
我知道
I know.
但你本来要去上学的
But you were going to school,
上大学
to college.
我理解你为什么放弃了
And I get why you gave it up.
但如果你不用放弃呢
But what if you didn't have to?
如果你可以有不一样的未来呢
What if there was a different future for you,
我们都可以有
for us?
这就是我这么做的原因  这就是我奋斗的目标
That's why I'm doing this. That is what I'm fighting for.
我不是想招募你
I am not trying to recruit you,
但你需要知道
but you need to know.
情况在变化
Things are changing.
求你
Please.
让我带你看看
Just let me show you.
就在这里
It's, uh, just in here.
相信吗  这还只是他们的临时基地
Believe it or not, this is just their temporary base.
听英国人的意思这条件算艰苦了
The Brits talk like they're roughing it.
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam Winchester.
你没说你儿子会过来
You didn't tell me your son was stopping by.
我不知道我还得报告
Didn't know I had to.
总之  欢迎
Anyway, welcome.
嗯  我是很喜欢
Yeah, um, you know, I really dig the whole
这低配《碟中谍》的风格  但我要回去了
low-budget Mission Impossible vibe, but I'm gonna head back.
真的
You sure?
你正好赶上任务报告
You're just in time for the briefing.
米克
Mick.
我是说  如果你想听听
I mean, that is, if you wanna hear
我们打算怎么清除全美境内所有的吸血鬼
how we're gonna exterminate every last vampire in America.
萨姆
Sammy?
露西  我...
Lucy! I...
出去了  待会儿回来
Went out, back later.
管他呢
Whatever.
糟糕
Oh, no.
-凯奇呢  -我不知道
- Where's Ketch? - I don't know.
他不在屋里  也不接电话
He wasn't in his room and isn't answering his mobile.
要等吗
Should we wait?
不了
No.
怎么  忘拿钥匙了吗
What'd, you forget your key?
你好  伙计
Hello, mate.
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
这可是记录者的地堡
Well, this is a Men of Letters bunker.
其位置对我们不是秘密
The location's no secret to us.
好吧
Okay.
好啊  聊天愉快
Cool. Well, good talk.
虽然我知道你对我
And whilst I understand that you're not feeling...
没什么好感  不知
warmly disposed to me, I wonder,
你对这瓶十分罕见
what's your disposition to this incredibly rare,
无比昂贵的
unspeakably expensive,
威士忌有什么想法
bottle of barrel proof Scotch?
开始之前  这里有几个新面孔
Before we get started, we've got a few new faces.
这位是皮尔斯·蒙克利夫
This is Pierce Moncrieff,
巴吞鲁日的一位猎人
a hunter out of Baton Rouge.
皮尔斯  这是奥尔顿·莫海德
Pierce meet Alton Morehead,
我们的研发部主管
our head of R&D --
武器研发  咒语  之类的
weapons development, spell work, that sort of thing.
这位是塞琳娜·科尔曼
And Serena Colman,
安保监控主管
our Head of Security and Surveillance.
当然了  你认识玛丽·温彻斯特
And, of course, you know Mary Winchester
还有她儿子
and her son.
萨姆  请坐吧
Sam, please. Plenty of seats.
不用了
I'm fine.
那好吧  我们开始
All right, then. Let's begin.
你们大都知道  V计划第一阶段几乎已完成
As most of you know, Phase One of Project V is nearly complete.
这几个月来  我们主要把精力
Over the past months, we've focused our efforts
-放在NWR上  -中西部
- on the NWR. - Midwest Region.
行动开始时
When we started our operation,
12州内有241个活跃吸血鬼
there were 241 vampires active across 12 states.
我们杀到了
We've killed all...
-只剩11个  -等等  什么
- but 11. - Wait, what?
不是吧
Seriously?
怎么做到的
How?
你们美国猎人
You American hunters
一般把吸血鬼视为罪犯  流氓
tend to see vampires as criminals, rogues.
有人不守规矩  你们就出现
One gets out of line, you show up,
砍头  然后走人
lop off its head, and leave town.
我们把他们视为恐怖分子
We treat them more like terrorists.
吸血鬼虽然一般独自猎食
Vampires may typically hunt alone
或是以小巢穴为单位
or in small nests.
但表面之下  他们都是互相有联系的
But scratch the surface, and they're all connected,
从最底层的工蜂
from the lowest drone
一直到最高层
all the way up the chain to the top.
始祖
To the Alpha.
我们发现一个巢穴后
When we find a nest,
我们不单单是带着枪炮冲进去
we don't just charge in a la John Wayne, guns a-blazing.
我们等待  观察
We wait, we watch.
确定巢穴人数
We determine the size of the nest,
以及和其他巢穴的关系
its relationships to other vampire groups.
他们一般会相互交易
They tend to trade amongst themselves --
信息  受害人
information, victims.
我们在不断扩充优化我们的情报
We're constantly expanding and refining our intelligence.
等我们了解到一切  就行动
And when we've learned all we can, we go,
-组织一支小队  -铲除他们
- we assemble a team - And wipe them out.
中西部其他吸血鬼都
Now all the remaining NWR vampires
住进了威奇托附近的一栋废弃大楼里
have bunkered up in an abandoned building near Wichita --
莫雷斯酒店
the Morest Hotel.
他们自以为安全
They think they're safe.
我们已经准备好了AVD
We've got the AVD locked and loaded.
AVD  抗吸血鬼装置
AVD -- Anti-Vamp Device.
明天  我们出发
Tomorrow, we ship out,
突袭大楼
raid the compound,
消灭巢穴  完成第一阶段
terminate the colony, and, uh, complete Phase One.
然后我们继续在全国开展行动
And then we move on to the rest of the country.
等我们完成
By the time we're done,
美国就不会再有一只吸血鬼了
there won't be a single bloodsucker left in America.
他们死了
They're dead.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
我整个巢穴
My whole nest.
我知道  亲爱的
I know, dear.
他们被杀了
They got them.
喝吧  能恢复你的力气
Drink. Get your strength back.
是新鲜人血
It's human and fresh.
你很安全
You're safe,
你和其他人
you and all the others.
我选择这地方可不是为了它的氛围
See, I didn't choose this place for its ambiance.
这不用说
Obviously.
这里
This?
是座堡垒
It's a fortress.
有人进来我都会发现
No one gets in here without me knowing about it.
绝无例外
No one.
是吗
Is that so?
你们好  我的孩子们
Hello, my children.
这地方不错  别致  舒适
Nice place. Quaint. Cozy.
不怎么喜欢闲聊  是吧
Not much for small talk, are we?
是啊
Nope.
你总会有问题想问吧
Well, surely, you have some questions.
比如我为什么来
Why I'm here, for instance.
你是来招募我们的
You're here to recruit us.
你已经把玛丽招过去了
You already got Mary playing your game.
你还想要我和萨姆
You want me. And Sam.
我不想  但老头子们很喜欢你们
Well, I don't, but the old lads have taken quite a shine to you.
那或许他们不该派个小妞
Well, maybe they shouldn't have sent some chick
过来杀我们
to try to kill us.
是啊  图妮
Yes -- Toni.
没人料到她会擅自行动  只有我猜到了
No one predicted she would go rogue. No one but me.
我早就看出了她是个神经质  眼高手低的
I had a sneak peak at what a neurotic, overreaching,
定时炸弹
time bomb she was.
我们约过会
We used to date.
看得出来
Yeah, I can see that.
迪恩  我才不在乎你来不来
Dean, I don't give a toss if you sign up.
老实说  我都不在乎你的死活
Honestly, I don't care if you live or die.
但既然我们现在关系这么好了
But since we're such jolly good pals now --
好吗
Jolly good, huh?
容我说  记录者
Let me just say that the Men of Letters
非常适合
is an excellent fit for
一个有我们这种
someone with our...
爱好的人
inclinations.
我们
Our.
你和我吗
As in you and me?
你是个杀手  迪恩·温彻斯特
You're a killer, Dean Winchester,
我也是
and so am I.
如果我们太久没有目标可追踪  困住
And if we go too long without something to track or trap
揍  或开膛  那就要不妙了
or punch or gut, well, things get a bit ugly.
是吧
Don't they?
记录者让我一直有活儿干
The Men of Letters keep me busy.
他们给我指个方向  我就开跑
They point me in a direction and bang. Off to the races.
这样的日子不错
It's not a bad life.
说起来
Speaking of...
既然你已经听过我要说的了
Now that you've heard what I have to say,
我还有事  还要砍吸血鬼的头
places to be, vampires to behead.
你有吸血鬼的线索
You got a line on vamps?
是啊
I do.
有兴趣吗
Interested?
我去  萨姆·温彻斯特
Damn. Sam Winchester.
鲁弗斯跟我讲过你好多事
Rufus told me all about you.
他和我在阿查法拉亚合作过一个案子
See, him and me worked a case together down the Atchafalaya.
我听说了
I heard.
告诉你  真怀念那个暴脾气的老混蛋
I tell ya, sure do miss that crotchety old son of a bitch.
皮尔斯  玛丽  有个问题
Pierce? Mary? A question.
怎么样
So?
对我们的行动有什么想法吗
Thoughts on our little operation?
我们的团队呢
And our team?
塞琳娜和奥尔顿似乎挺聪明
Serena and Alton seem smart.
皮尔斯
Pierce...
你知道他自称巴吞鲁日猎人之王吗
You know he calls himself the hunter king of Baton Rouge?
很不幸  我知道
I do. Unfortunately.
我的一个伙计认识他  他们合作过
A buddy of mine knew him. They worked together.
就一次
Once.
嗯  事实上  除了你妈妈
Right, you see, truth is, your mother excepted,
我们实在吸引不来
we've struggled to attract the, uh,
顶尖的美国猎人
top shelf of American Hunters.
比如你
Like you.
(米克: 你去哪了)
什么情况
So what do we got?
大概10个吸血鬼
10 bloodsuckers, give or take.
2对10  赢面挺大
2 against 10. I like those odds.
是啊  一小时后就日落了
Yeah, the sun'll be down in an hour,
我们该快点行动
so we should move fast.
别让老鼠弃船逃跑
Keep the rats from fleeing the ship.
真高档
Fancy.
是啊  这样太简单了
You're right. This is too easy.
那个还有吗
Got another of those?
-准备好了吗  -时刻就绪
- Ready? - ‭Always.
似乎没人
Place seems empty.
是啊
Yes.
奇怪
Curious.
萨姆  这就是为什么我叫你来
Sam, this is why I asked you to come.
就算你不想参与  你也该知道
Even if you want no part of it, you needed to know.
不是在招安吗
So it wasn't a sales pitch?
因为挺有说服力的
'Cause it was a good one.
我查过楼上了  这里没人
I checked the areas upstairs. This place is a ghost town.
-你有发现吗  -有
- You got anything? - ‭Indeed.
她在地下室  跟尸体藏在一起
I found her hiding in the basement with the corpses.
放了我
Let me go! ‭
你的朋友呢
Where are your friends?
我不知道
I don't know.
他们在哪
Where are they?
告诉
Tell...
我
me...
快说
now.
好了  够了
Okay. All right, that's enough.
够了  她是个怪物
Enough? She's a monster.
我知道
I know.
让我来
Just...let me.
你得告诉我们你的朋友在哪
You're gonna need to tell us where your friends are.
然后你就放了我吗
And you'll let me go?
我会利落点
I'll make it quick.
猎食  他们去猎食了
Hunting. They went hunting.
猎食谁
Hunting whom?
猎人
The Hunters.
麦克吉勒嘉迪呢
Where's McGillicuddy?
怎么回事
What's happening?
是莫雷斯的吸血鬼
It's the Morest vampires.
他们来这儿了
They're here.
(准入)
糟糕
No.
我们得马上封锁这里
We gotta lock this place down, ASAP.
撤退
Fall back.
马上封锁
Lock this place down now!
撤退  守住各出口
Fall back. Secure all exits.
不要交火  马上撤退
Do not engage. Fall back now.
很好
Nice.
(准入)
(待机)
等等
Wait!
Wait.
-门锁了吗  -暂时是的
- Doors locked? - ‭For now.
其余的
The rest,
他们散开了  包围了大楼
they're spreading out, surrounding the building.
他们怎么找来的
How'd they find us?
他们怎么会知道我们的身份
How'd they even know who we are?
他告诉我们的
He told us.
他回来拯救我们了
He's back to save us all.
我们的父亲
Our father.
你的父亲
Your father?
始祖吗
The -- the Alpha?
不  那不可能  我们的情报显示他在摩洛哥
No, that's impossible. Our intel has him in -- in Morocco.
他至少在那里待了十年了
He's been there for at least a decade.
错了
Wrong.
我五年前在北达科他州虎帕见过他
I met him five years ago in Hoople, North Dakota.
你们死定了
You're dead.
你们都死定了
You're all dead.
你的清除计划
Your, uh, extermination plan,
有针对这种情况的紧急预案吗
did it have any contingencies for this?
没有
No.
通讯依然中断
Comm's still out.
占卜咒呢
What about a scrying spell?
如果我们能送信去英国
If we can get a message to England --
-不行  我们不能等支援  -他说得对
- No, we can't wait for backup. - No, he's right.
这里不具备防卫能力
This place was not built for defense,
那些门坚持不了多久
and those doors will not hold long.
好吧
Okay.
这里谁杀过
Who here has ever killed...
什么东西
anything?
太好了
Great.
好吧  我们得拿装备
All right, we gotta arm up.
所有人  把武器放桌上
Everybody, weapons on the table.
刀  枪  咒语
Blades, guns, spells.
-就这些  -对
- Is this it? - ‭Yeah.
这不够
That's not enough.
我们大部分武器在军械库  包括AVD
Most of our weapons are in the Armory, including the AVD.
我们可以在通风管里引爆它
We could set it off in the vents.
最大化扩散  把毒气当杀虫弹用
Maximize coverage, use the gas like the bug bomb.
那能杀死始祖吗
Will that kill the Alpha?
杀死  恐怕不会  致伤  还有可能
Kill? Doubt it. Hurt? Maybe.
你有更厉害的东西吗
You got anything stronger?
在哪呢
Where is it?
你从哪拿到的
Where'd you get this?
我偷来的
I stole it.
从雷米尔那儿
From Ramiel.
是啊  但没用
Yeah, but it doesn't work.
我们没有子弹
We've no bullets.
是啊
Right.
你说得对
You're right.
嗯
Right, um...
好  那我们做吧
Okay. We make some, then.
我从朋友那儿弄来的配方
Got the recipe from my buddy.
-鲍比·辛格  -对
- Bobby Singer? - ‭Yep.
好了  米克  你需要圣油  鼠尾草和没药
All right, Mick, you're gonna need holy oil, sage, and myrrh.
-这里有吗  -有
- Do you have that here? - ‭Yeah.
好的  做成酊剂  涂在银色子弹上
Okay, uh, make a tincture, coat a silver bullet.
用这个咒语  可以模仿原始蚀刻
Use this spell. It'll mimic the original etchings.
-能成功吗  -最好成功
- And that'll work? - It better.
否则  就祈祷吧  因为我们会需要奇迹
If not, start praying, 'cause we'll need a miracle.
-军械库在哪  -我带你去
- Where's the Armory? - I'll take you.
我掩护你们
I got your back.
开工  门锁好
Get to work. Keep that door locked.
这边来
This way!
军械库就在外面
The Armory's out there.
还有别的路吗  还有别的路吗
Is there another way? Is there another way?!
后边
Back there!
去吧  我挡得住
Go! I got 'em.
走吧
Come on, come on, come on!
好了
All right.
开始施咒吧
Let's get this spell going.
拿到了
Got it.
[咒语]
是我  开门
It's me! Open the damn door!
怎么回事
What happened?
情况很糟
It's bad out there.
这里也不妙
Pretty bad in here, too, huh?
不
No.
皮尔斯  你是个猎人
Pierce, you're a Hunter.
对  我的猎人
Yes. My hunter.
皮尔斯和我有个约定
Pierce and I have an arrangement.
他掩护我
He keeps me off the radar,
我给他很好的酬劳
and I pay him very, very well.
赡养费太难搞了
Alimony's a bitch.
我老了
I'm old.
我喜欢安静生活
I like living quietly.
而你最近让我的生活非常吵闹
You've been making my life awfully noisy lately.
你杀了好多我的孩子
You've killed so many of my children.
我见识过你的工作
I've seen your work.
在英国
In England,
我没插手
I didn't get involved
因为
because, well...
那是英国
it's England.
但美国
But America...
没错
yes.
美国是我的家
America is my home.
现在
And it's time
你该滚出
that you...get...off...
我家了
my lawn.
妈妈  妈妈
Mom? Mom.
妈妈  你没事吧
Mom, hey. Are you all right?
萨姆
Sam.
怎么回事
‭What happened?
拿到了
Got it.
这里安全了  老大
All clear here, big daddy.
我们得走了
We have to go.
好的  走吧
Yeah, right. All right.
来吧  我扶你
Come on. ‭I got you.
听好了
Here's what you're going to do.
我们会恢复你的通讯
We will bring your communications back online.
你打给你伦敦的上级
You will make a call to your superiors in London.
承认失败
You'll admit defeat.
告诉他们取消对美国的入侵
You will tell them to cancel this American incursion.
然后让他们看着
Then they'll watch
我在屏幕上把你活吞下去
as I devour you, live, onscreen.
是啊  是有点不堪
Yes, it's a bit messy,
但有时候需要表明立场
but sometimes one does have to make a point.
别
Don't!
天呐
My, my.
柯尔特枪
The Colt.
厉害的武器
Powerful weapon.
萨姆  你知道这世上有五个生灵
Sam, you are aware that there are five creatures on this Earth
那枪杀不死吧
that gun cannot kill.
我就是其中之一
I'm one of them.
若果真如此  我这会儿已经死了
If that were true, I'd be dead already.
那枪救不了你们所有人
That gun can't save all of you.
谁说我想救所有人了
Who said I was here to save all of us?
我们家的人  杀出格的吸血鬼
My family and I, we kill vamps when they get out of line.
你一直没管我们
And you've let us.
我有很多孩子  萨姆
I have many children, Sam.
死一两个又如何
What's one, two, here or there?
没错
Exactly.
那么
So?
放了我和我妈
Let my mom and me go.
我们会离开
We'll walk away,
恢复以前的秩序
go back to the way things were,
本该有的秩序
to the way things are supposed to be.
猎人和吸血鬼  警察和劫匪
Hunters and vampires, cops and robbers,
公平斗争
a fair fight.
英国人呢
And the Brit?
给你了
You can have him.
萨姆  你干什么
Sam. What are you doing?
选择立场
Picking a side.
你个混蛋
You bastard.
妈妈
Mom!
萨姆
Sam...
你和我都知道那枪里没子弹
you and I both know that gun isn't loaded.
你确定吗
You sure?
那枪救不了你们所有人
The gun can't save all of you.
谁说我想救所有人了
Who said I was here to save all of us?
混蛋
Bastard.
不
No.
真聪明
Clever, clever boy.
米克
Mick.
外面安全了
All clear out there.
干掉几个逃兵
Took out a few stragglers.
其他的肯定是我们杀死始祖后跑了
The rest must've run when we dropped the Alpha.
走吧
Come on.
你去哪了
Where were you?
听从命令
Following orders.
这...有人死了
That's not... People died.
是啊  我不知道你的象牙塔里什么样
Yes. Well, I don't know how it is in your ivory tower,
但在实战中  就是会死人的
but down here in the muck, people die.
长老要温家人
The old men want the Winchesters,
我就去争取迪恩了
so I made a play for Dean,
本来挺成功  结果你的行动出了岔子
and it was working until your operation went sideways.
好了
Oh, well. ‭
下次会更走运
Better luck next time.
"出去了  待会儿回来"是吧
So "went out, back later," huh?
就是去喝杯酒  是吗
Just getting a drink, huh?
我听说这里遭袭时  正好跟他在一起
I was with him when we heard this place was under attack.
我们飞速赶过来了
We drove like a bat out of hell.
怎么会
How come?
你并不在乎他们
I mean, you don't care for these guys.
你又不知道我在这儿
You didn't even know I was here.
当然了
Right, of course.
我一想到你可能会出事
When I thought something might've happened to you,
其他都无所谓了
nothing else mattered.
迪恩  我说的话
Dean, the things I said --
不  妈妈  你...
No, Mom, you were...
你的职责已经不是给我做午饭
It's not your job to make my lunch and...
晚上吻别道晚安了
kiss me good night. It's...
我们是成年人
We're adults.
你会做出自己的选择
You're gonna make your own choices,
哪怕我不满
even if I don't like 'em.
哪怕我真的很不满
Even if I really, really don't like 'em.
我只能接受这一点
That's just something I'm gonna have to get used to.
好吗  妈妈
Okay, Mom?
好
Yeah.
你带他去哪
Where you takin' him?
我们有些对付叛徒猎人的办法
We have ways of dealing with hunters who go rogue.
不愉快的办法
They aren't pleasant.
-很好  -很好
- Good. - Good.
萨姆
Sam.
今晚如果不是有你
If you hadn't been there tonight...
我们杀了他们  这才最重要
Yeah, we got the kill. That's what matters.
但对于英国记录者来说  不算是好广告
Hardly an advertisement for the British Men of Letters, though.
对我的领导水平也不是
Or my leadership.
完全被打了个措手不及
Caught unawares with our proverbial pants down.
-不管你信不信  萨姆  -我加入
- Believe it or not, Sam, we're not - I'm in.
今晚的确很糟糕
Look, tonight was bad, no doubt,
但始祖吸血鬼死了
but the Alpha Vampire is dead.
你们在改变世界  我想加入进来
You're changing the world, and I wanna be a part of it.
你哥哥呢
And your brother?
给我点时间
Give me some time.